export const easy = [
  {
    question: "What is the probability of getting heads in a coin toss?",
    options: ["0", "0.5", "1", "2"],
    answer: "0.5"
  },
  {
    question: "A die is rolled. What is the probability of getting 3?",
    options: ["1/6", "1/3", "1/2", "1/5"],
    answer: "1/6"
  },
  {
    question: "Probability ranges between:",
    options: ["0 to 1", "1 to 2", "-1 to 1", "0 to âˆž"],
    answer: "0 to 1"
  },
  {
    question: "A bag has 5 red balls and 5 green balls. P(getting red) = ?",
    options: ["0.1", "0.5", "1", "0.2"],
    answer: "0.5"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the probability of getting an even number when a die is thrown?",
    options: ["1/6", "1/3", "1/2", "2/3"],
    answer: "1/2"
  }
];

export const medium = [
  {
    question: "Two coins are tossed. What is the probability of getting two heads?",
    options: ["1/4", "1/2", "1/3", "2/3"],
    answer: "1/4"
  },
  {
    question: "A card is drawn from a deck. What is the probability of getting a king?",
    options: ["1/13", "1/26", "1/52", "4/13"],
    answer: "1/13"
  },
  {
    question: "There are 3 red and 2 blue balls. P(blue) = ?",
    options: ["2/5", "1/2", "3/5", "2/3"],
    answer: "2/5"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the probability of getting a prime number on a die?",
    options: ["1/6", "1/2", "2/3", "1/3"],
    answer: "1/2"
  },
  {
    question: "If an event is impossible, its probability is:",
    options: ["1", "0", "0.5", "None"],
    answer: "0"
  }
];

export const hard = [
  {
    question: "In a class of 20, 7 are girls. One student is picked. P(girl) = ?",
    options: ["7/20", "13/20", "1/2", "2/5"],
    answer: "7/20"
  },
  {
    question: "Two dice are rolled. P(sum = 7)?",
    options: ["1/6", "1/12", "1/36", "1/18"],
    answer: "1/6"
  },
  {
    question: "Probability of getting a vowel in word 'MATH'?",
    options: ["1/4", "1/2", "3/4", "1/3"],
    answer: "1/4"
  },
  {
    question: "A number is picked from 1 to 10. P(even) = ?",
    options: ["1/2", "2/5", "3/5", "4/5"],
    answer: "1/2"
  },
  {
    question: "P(E) = 0.7, what is P(not E)?",
    options: ["0.3", "0.7", "1", "0.5"],
    answer: "0.3"
  }
];
